Guide to The Polytechnic Reporter RG.025
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series I: Loose newspapers
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 November 25, 12482 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 December 3, 12483 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 December 9, 12484 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 December 16, 12485 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 December 23, 12486 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 January 6, 12487 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 January 14, 12488 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 February 3, 12489 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 February 10, 12490 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 February 17, 12491 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 February 25, 12492 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 March 3, 12493 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 March 10, 12494 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 March 17, 12495 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 March 24, 12496 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 March 31, 12497 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 April 14, 12498 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 April 21, 12499 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 April 28, 12500 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 May 5, 12501 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 May 12, 12502 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 September 23, 12503 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 September 29, 12504 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 October 6, 12505 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 October 14, 12506 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 October 20, 12507 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 October 27, 12508 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 November 4, 12509 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 November 10, 12510 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 November 17, 12511 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 November 24, 12512 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 December 1, 12513 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 December 8, 12514 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 December 15, 12515 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 January 5, 12516 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 January 12, 12517 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 February 9, 12518 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 February 16, 12519 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 February 23, 12520 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 March 2, 12521 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 March 9, 12522 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 March 16, 12523 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 March 23, 12524 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 March 30, 12525 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 April 6, 12526 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 April 13, 12527 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 May 4, 12528 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 May 11, 12529 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 May 18, 12530 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1941 May 7, 12531 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1941 June 11, 12532 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1941 September 24, 12533 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 April 10, 12612 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 May 1, 12613 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 September 11, 12614 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 September 25, 12615 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 October 3, 12616 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 October 10, 12617 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 October 16, 12618 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 October 24, 12619 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 October 31, 12620 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 November 6, 12621 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 November 13, 12622 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 November 20, 12623 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 November 26, 12624 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 December 4, 12625 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 December 4 (Special Issue), 12626 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 December 12, 12627 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 December 19, 12628 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 January 30, 12629 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 February 6, 12630 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 February 12, 12631 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 February 27, 12632 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 March 4, 12633 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 March 12, 12634 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 March 18, 12635 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 March 25, 12636 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 April 1, 12637 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 April 9, 12638 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 April 23, 12639 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 April 30, 12640 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 May 11, 12641 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Fall 1976 (Special Registration Issue), 1976 Fall; 12642 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 September 24, 12643 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 October 1, 12644 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 October 8, 12645 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 October 22, 12646 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 October 29, 12647 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 November 5, 12648 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 November 12, 12649 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 November 19, 12650 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 December 16, 12651 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 December 23, 12652 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Status of the Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 December; 12653 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 January 28, 12654 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 February 4, 12655 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 February 18, 12656 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 March 4, 12657 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 March 11, 12658 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 March 18, 12659 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 March 25, 12660 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pyrotepnic Reporter, 1977 April 0?, 13024 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 April 7, 12661 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 April 22, 12662 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 April 29, 12663 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 May 6, 12664 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 September 16, 12665 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 September 23, 12666 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 September 30, 12667 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 October 7, 12668 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 October 14, 12669 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 October 21, 12670 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 October 28, 12671 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 November 4, 12672 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 November 11, 12673 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 November 18, 12674 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 November 23, 12675 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 December 2, 12676 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 December 9, 12677 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 December 16, 12678 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 December 23, 12679 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 February 3, 12680 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 February 10, 12681 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 February 17, 12682 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 February 24, 12683 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 March 3, 13025 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 March 10, 12684 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 March 17, 12685 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 March 23, 12686 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 April 7, 12687 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 April 14, 12688 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 April 21, 12689 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 April 27, 12690 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 May 5, 12691 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 September 15, 12692 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 September 22, 12693 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 September 29, 12694 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 October 6, 12695 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 October 13, 12696 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 October 20, 12697 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Polytechnic Reporter, 1994 February 9
  - Polytechnic Reporter, 2003 April 23
  - Polytechnic Reporter, 2003 September 17
- Series II: Bound newspapers
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 6, No. 1-29 (bound), 1918-1919; 12420 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 7, No. 1-26 (bound), 1919-1920; 12421 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 8, No. 1-28 (bound), 1920-1921; 12422 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 9, No. 1-29 (bound), 1921-1922; 12423 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 11 (bound), 1923-1924; 12424 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 12 (bound), 1924-1925; 12425 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 14, No. 1-27 (bound), 1926-1927; 12426 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 15 (bound), 1927-1928; 12427 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 16 (bound), 1928-1929; 12428 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 17 (bound), 1929-1930; 12429 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 10)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 18 (bound), 1930-1931; 12430 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 11)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 19 (bound), 1931-1932; 12431 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 12)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 20 (bound), 1932-1933; 12432 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 13)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 21 (bound), 1933-1934; 12433 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 14)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 22 (bound), 1934-1935; 12434 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 15)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 23 (bound), 1935-1936; 12435 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 16)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 24 (bound), 1936-1937; 12436 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 17)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 25 (bound), 1937-1938; 12437 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 18)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 26 (bound), 1938-1939; 12438 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 19)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 30 (bound), 1939-1940; 12439 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 20)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 31 (bound), 1940-1941; 12440 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 21)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 32 (bound), 1941-1942; 12441 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 22)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 33 (bound), 1942-1943; 12442 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 23)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 35-39 (bound), 1944-1946; 12443 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 24)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 40 (bound), 1947-1948; 12444 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 25)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 41 (bound), 1948-1949; 12445 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 26)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 43 (bound), 1950-1951; 12446 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 27)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 46 (bound), 1953-1954; 12447 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 28)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 47 (bound), 1954-1955; 12448 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 29)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 48 (bound), 1955-1956; 12449 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 30)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 50 (bound), 1957-1958; 12450 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 31)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 51 (bound), 1958-1959; 12451 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 32)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 52 (bound), 1959-1960; 12452 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 33)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 53 (bound), 1960-1961; 12453 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 34)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 54 (bound), 1961-1962; 12454 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 35)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 55 (bound), 1962-1963; 12455 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 36)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 56 (bound), 1963-1964; 12456 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 37)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 57 (bound), 1964-1965; 12457 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 38)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 58 (bound), 1965-1966; 12458 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 39)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 59 (bound), 1966-1967; 12459 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 40)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 60 (bound), 1967-1968; 12460 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 41)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 61 (bound), 1968-1969; 12461 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 42)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 62 (bound), 1969-1970; 12462 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 43)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 63 (bound), 1970-1971; 12463 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 44)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 64 (bound), 1971-1972; 12464 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 45)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 65 (bound), 1972-1973; 12465 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 46)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 66 (bound), 1973-1974; 12466 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 47)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 67 (bound), 1974-1975; 12467 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 48)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 1, No. 1-12 (new iteration of the paper), 1979; 12468 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 49)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Index A-K, undated; 12469 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 50)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Index L-Z, undated; 12470 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 51)